excoboard.com 2018-09-30

# Privacy Policy – Excoboard

#### Privacy Statement for Excoboard

Excoboard has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for Excoboard. 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. 

Our site uses cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. 

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address). The customer's contact information may be used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings by requesting it to [support](http://excoboard.com/contact/). 

This site contains links to other sites. Excoboard is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://excoboard.com/terms-of-service/). 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on their visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/). 

Public Forums  
This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

Security  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. 

Contacting the Web Site  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can [contact support](http://excoboard.com/contact/).
